export const AhmedabadFaq = [
    {
        question: "What areas TruckMeru serve in Ahmedabad?",
        answer:
          "Bakrol Bujrang, Kathwada GIDC, Vatva GIDC, Bavla, Changodar, Santej, Sanand, Kheda, Bareja, Sanathal, Sarkhej, Zak GIDC, Talod, Kadi, Kalol, Chattral GIDC.",
      },
      {
        question: "What types of goods can you transport?",
        answer:
          "We handle a wide range of goods, including industrial materials, textiles, chemicals, pharmaceuticals, and more.",
      },
      {
        question: "How can I book your transport service?",
        answer:
          "You can book our transport services by contacting us via phone, email, or through our website's booking form.",
      },
];




export const Ahmedabadcities = [
   
    'Gandhidham', 'Delhi', 'Gurugram', 'Noida',
    'Jaipur', 'Jodhpur', 'Chennai', 'Bangalore',
    'Hyderabad', 'Mumbai', 'Pune', 'Kanpur',
    'Lucknow', 'Patna', 'Ajmer', 'Vijayawada'
  ];





// Mumbai Section

export const MumbaiFaq = [
    {
        question: "What areas do you serve in Mumbai?",
        answer:
          "We provide transport services across all major areas in Mumbai and surrounding regions.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the average delivery time for shipments?",
        answer:
          "Delivery times depend on distance and traffic, but we try to meet our timelines.",
      },
      {
        question: "Can I get a quote before booking?",
        answer:
          "Yes, you can request a free quote by providing details about your transport needs.",
      },
      {
        question: "What should I do if there’s a delay?",
        answer:
          "If there’s a delay, please contact our customer service team for updates and assistance.",
      },
];

export const Mumbaicities = [
    'Banglore', 'Haridwar'
  ];


  export const DelhiFaq = [
    {
        question: "What areas do you serve in Mumbai?",
        answer:
          "We provide transport services across all major areas in Mumbai and surrounding regions.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the average delivery time for shipments?",
        answer:
          "Delivery times depend on distance and traffic, but we try to meet our timelines.",
      },
      {
        question: "Can I get a quote before booking?",
        answer:
          "Yes, you can request a free quote by providing details about your transport needs.",
      },
      {
        question: "What should I do if there’s a delay?",
        answer:
          "If there’s a delay, please contact our customer service team for updates and assistance.",
      },
];

export const Delhicities = [
  'Banglore', 'Haridwar'
];


  export const PuneFaq = [
    {
        question: "What areas do you serve in Mumbai?",
        answer:
          "We provide transport services across all major areas in Mumbai and surrounding regions.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the average delivery time for shipments?",
        answer:
          "Delivery times depend on distance and traffic, but we try to meet our timelines.",
      },
      {
        question: "Can I get a quote before booking?",
        answer:
          "Yes, you can request a free quote by providing details about your transport needs.",
      },
      {
        question: "What should I do if there’s a delay?",
        answer:
          "If there’s a delay, please contact our customer service team for updates and assistance.",
      },
];

export const Punecities = [
  'Banglore', 'Haridwar'
];

  export const ChennaiFaq = [
    {
        question: "What areas do you serve in Mumbai?",
        answer:
          "We provide transport services across all major areas in Mumbai and surrounding regions.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the average delivery time for shipments?",
        answer:
          "Delivery times depend on distance and traffic, but we try to meet our timelines.",
      },
      {
        question: "Can I get a quote before booking?",
        answer:
          "Yes, you can request a free quote by providing details about your transport needs.",
      },
      {
        question: "What should I do if there’s a delay?",
        answer:
          "If there’s a delay, please contact our customer service team for updates and assistance.",
      },
];

export const Chennaicities = [
  'Banglore', 'Haridwar'
];

  export const HyderabadFaq = [
    {
        question: "What areas do you serve in Mumbai?",
        answer:
          "We provide transport services across all major areas in Mumbai and surrounding regions.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the average delivery time for shipments?",
        answer:
          "Delivery times depend on distance and traffic, but we try to meet our timelines.",
      },
      {
        question: "Can I get a quote before booking?",
        answer:
          "Yes, you can request a free quote by providing details about your transport needs.",
      },
      {
        question: "What should I do if there’s a delay?",
        answer:
          "If there’s a delay, please contact our customer service team for updates and assistance.",
      },
];

export const Hyderabadcities = [
  'Banglore', 'Haridwar'
];


export const MainFaq = [
  {
      question: "What areas do you serve in Mumbai?",
      answer:
        "We provide transport services across all major areas in Mumbai and surrounding regions.",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the average delivery time for shipments?",
      answer:
        "Delivery times depend on distance and traffic, but we try to meet our timelines.",
    },
    {
      question: "Can I get a quote before booking?",
      answer:
        "Yes, you can request a free quote by providing details about your transport needs.",
    },
    {
      question: "What should I do if there’s a delay?",
      answer:
        "If there’s a delay, please contact our customer service team for updates and assistance.",
    },
];





